[{"answer": "What's goin' on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Did you get a thank you wave", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Give me that wave", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yeah, I'm free, why", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You can't let him get away with that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What are you, yellow", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "By the way, my friend does not need to know about anything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Oh, you dig", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "With that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What car", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Oh, right, right, right, right, right, right, right, the hit and run. Well. Actually, the guy went into that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Over the bridge. ", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well he kinda lost his temper, and he was pushing me up against the car. So I went into a karate stance.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I know a little", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "They should be sent to that place.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Yeah, yeah, that's where that place used to send their convicts", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "He was only joking my friend! Sorry", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I am not taking his side", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "All right! Take his side", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well who's side are you taking?", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I am not taking his side", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Well I'm not taking your side! ", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Whatever", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah, yeah, that's better than 'God bless you'. Anyway, she left a message on my machine, she wants you to call her", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hey, grab my friend's sweater for me, would you?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Chilly out", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Chilly out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yeah, you can take a sweater if you want to", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What car", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You can't compromise your principles", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Can't live", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "No, never", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Good-Samaritan.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "You got a date with my friend?", "qsentId": 34}]